https://edwardwillett.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
What Information Does This Site Collect?
Newsletter
If you voluntarily sign up for Edward Willett’s newsletter, this site will record your email address. When subscribers click on a link in one of these emails or fill out a form, the site may record this information (see below how this information is used).
Subscribers may unsubscribe at any time. You may ask for all your data to be deleted at any time.
Giveaways and Contests
If you enter a giveaway, your email address is collected. If you win a physical prize, you will be asked to give your name and physical address.
Non-personal Information
This website may collect non-personal information about visitors when they interact with the site. This information may include the browser name, means of connection to the site, and other non-identifying information.
Cookies
This website may use “cookies” to enhance visitor experience. Typically, cookies may be placed on visitors’ hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. Visitors may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to send an alert when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the site may not function properly.
How Is the Information Used?
Newsletter subscribers’ names and emails will only be used for receiving the newsletter or communication from Edward Willett.
Giveaway entrants will be sent emails only about the giveaway, unless they also signed up for the newsletter.
Information on which email links are clicked on the most will help Edward Willett choose links that interest readers in future emails.
Sharing of Personal Information
Subscriber information is never shared with a third party.
Third-party links
Sometimes Edward Willett will include third-party links through email or on the website. These sites have their own policies and you should read those before subscribing or purchasing from them.
Security of Information
Only Edward Willett can access saved information. Should a data breach ever occur, subscribers will be notified within seven days. (Again, all payments are processed through PayPal; read their privacy policy here.)
Changes to This Privacy Policy
Edward Willett may update this privacy policy at any time. A notice about such changes will be posted prominently on the site. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this Privacy Policy periodically and become aware of modifications.
Your Acceptance of These Terms
By visiting and using shadowpawpress.com, you signify your acceptance of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree, you can simply not use the site. Continued use of the site means you accept the policy and any periodic changes.
Questions?
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or anything else on shadowpawpress.com, please email edward@edwardwillett.com.
Permanent link to this article: https://edwardwillett.com/privacy-policy/
Looking for an editor or mentor?
I offer developmental and copyediting services as well as writing mentorships.
Email me!Subscribe to my newsletter
Email Address
Read previous newsletters.
Buy Autographed BooksListen to My PodcastTHE WORLDSHAPERS
Conversations with science fiction and fantasy authors about the creative processMost Recent Episodes
Episode 72: Cory Doctorow
An hour-long chat with Cory Doctorow, science-fiction author, activist, and journalist, about his creative process. Websitewww.craphound,com Blogwww.pluralistic.net Twitter@Doctorow Cory Doctorow’s Amazon Page The Introduction Cory Doctorow is a science fiction author, activist, and journalist. His latest book is Attack Surface, a standalone adult sequel to Little Brother. He is also the author How to Destroy…
https://media.blubrry.com/theworldshapers/content.blubrry.com/theworldshapers/TWS72-2020-12-06-CoryDoctorow.mp3
Episode 71: Patricia C. Wrede
An hour-and-twenty-minute interview with Patricia C. Wrede, award-winning author of more than twenty-two fantasy novels for readers of all ages, as well as two collections of short stories and one book on writing. Websitepcwrede.com Twitter@PatriciaCWrede Facebook@PatriciaWredeAuthor Patricia C. Wrede’s Amazon Page Patricia will be instructing the workshop “Worldbuilding in Fantasy and Science Fiction” for Odyssey…
https://media.blubrry.com/theworldshapers/content.blubrry.com/theworldshapers/TWS71-2020-11-29-PatriciaCWrede.mp3
Episode 70: F. Paul Wilson
An hour-long interview with F. Paul Wilson, the award-winning, bestselling author of 60 books and nearly 100 short stories spanning science fiction, horror, adventure, medical thrillers, and virtually everything between. WebsiteRepairmanJack.com Facebook@RealFPaulWilson Twitter@FPaulWilson F. Paul Wilson’s Amazon Page The Introduction F. Paul Wilson is the award-winning, bestselling author of 60 books and nearly 100 short…
https://media.blubrry.com/theworldshapers/content.blubrry.com/theworldshapers/TWS70-2020-11-15-FPaulWilson_01.mp3
Episode 69: Glen Zipper & Elaine Mongeon
An hour-long conversation with Elaine Mongeon and Glen Zipper, filmmakers, screenwriters, and authors of the new young-adult space-opera novel Devastation Class, first book in a trilogy from Blink. Websitewww.devastationclass.com Twitter@E_Mongeon@Zipper Instagram@ElaineMongeon@GlenZipper The Introduction Award-winning filmmaker Elaine Mongeon wrote and directed the short films Good Morning for Warner Bros. Pictures and Swiped to Death for Hulu and the Sundance Institute. She also…
https://media.blubrry.com/theworldshapers/content.blubrry.com/theworldshapers/TWS69-2020-11-01-ZipperMongeon.mp3
Episode 68: James Morrow
An hour-plus interview with James Morrow, World Fantasy Award, Nebula Award, Theodore Sturgeon Memorial Award and Grand prix de l’Imaginaire-winning author of eleven novels and many shorter works. Websitewww.jamesmorrow.net Facebook@james.morrow.754570 Twitter@jimmorrow11 James Morrow’s Amazon Page The Introduction Born in 1947, James Morrow has been writing fiction ever since. As a seven-year-old living in the Philadelphia…
https://media.blubrry.com/theworldshapers/content.blubrry.com/theworldshapers/TWS68-2020-10-25-JamesMorrow.mp3
Episode 67: Griffin Barber
An hour-long interview with Griffin Barber, author of Second Chance Angel, co-authored with Kacey Ezell; 1636: Mission to the Mughals, co-authored with Eric Flint, and Man-Eater, Book 3 of the Murphy’s Lawless series, set in Dr. Charles E. Gannon‘s Caine Riordan universe, and several short stories. Websitewww.griffinbarber.com Facebook@Griffin911 Twitter@J_GriffinB@RantingGriffin Griffin Barber’s Amazon Page Introduction Griffin…
https://media.blubrry.com/theworldshapers/content.blubrry.com/theworldshapers/TWS67-2020-10-18-GriffinBarber.mp3
Episode 66: Kacey Ezell
An hour-long conversation with Kacey Ezell, an active-duty USAF instructor helicopter pilot who writes sci-fi/fantasy/horror/noir/alternate history fiction including Minds of Men and The World Asunder, both Dragon Award Finalists for Best Alternate History in 2018 and 2019, respectively, and, with Griffin Barber, the far-future noir thriller Second Chance Angel. Websitewww.kaceyezell.net Facebook@KaceyEzell Instagram@KaceyEzell Kacey Ezell’s Amazon Page The Introduction…
https://media.blubrry.com/theworldshapers/content.blubrry.com/theworldshapers/TWS66-2020-10-04-KaceyEzell.mp3
Episode 65: Cat Rambo
A 45-minute chat with Cat Rambo, Nebula Award-winning author of more than 200 published short stories and several novels, editor, writing teacher, and past president of the Science Fiction and Fantasy Writers of America, about her creative process. Websitewww.catrambo.com Twitter@catrambo Facebook@catrambo Cat Rambo’s Amazon Page The Introduction Cat Rambo’s more than 200 published short stories…
https://media.blubrry.com/theworldshapers/content.blubrry.com/theworldshapers/TWS65-2020-09-26-CatRambo.mp3
Episode 64: R. B. Lemberg
An hour-long conversation with R.B. Lemberg, a linguist, and author of many stories set in the Birdverse, an LGBTQIA+-focused secondary world, including The Four Profound Weaves, a novella just released by Tachyon Publications. Website:rblemberg.net Twitter:@rb_lemberg Patreon:rblemberg R.B. Lemberg’s Amazon Page The Introduction R.B. Lemberg is a queer, bigender immigrant from Ukraine, Russia, and Israel to the US. Their…
https://media.blubrry.com/theworldshapers/content.blubrry.com/theworldshapers/TWS64-2020-09-19-RBLemberg.mp3
Episode 63: Kathrin Hutson
An hour-long conversation with Kathrin Hutson, internationally bestselling author of dark fantasy, science fiction, and LGBTQ+ speculative fiction, ghostwriter, fiction co-editor of Mud Season Review, and director of interviews for TopShelf Magazine. Websitekathrinhutsonfiction.com Facebook@KathrinHutsonFiction Instagram@KathrinHutsonFiction Twitter@ExquisitelyDark Kathrin Hutson’s Amazon Page The Introduction International bestselling author Kathrin Hutson has been writing dark fantasy, sci-fi, and LGBTQ…
https://media.blubrry.com/theworldshapers/content.blubrry.com/theworldshapers/TWS63-2020-09-12-KathrinHutson.mp3
Support me through Patreon!Patreon is a way for people to support creators in the creation of the stuff they create. You can now help me create science fiction and fantasy. Check out my Patreon page, and thanks!My Agent
Ethan Ellenberg
155 Suffolk St., #2R
New York, NY 10002
(212) 431-4554
agent@ethanellenberg.com
My Publicist
Mickey Mikkelson
Creative Edge
by Graphene Themes.
